{
    "id": "f0c29fae125c47138674b6a1027aee94",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James went to see his old friend ………………….. to discover that he had already left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "alone",
                "only",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ties that bind us together are so ………………… that they can rupture at any moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tentative",
                "tenuous",
                "restrictive"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There was nothing …………………… .. about her reaction to his marriage proposal. She rejected it ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "surprising, vehemently",
                "interesting, violently",
                "unpredictable, abruptly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The directions that he gave us were so …………………… . that we didn’t know which of the two roads to take.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complicated",
                "circuitous",
                "ambiguous"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It will be difficult for an …………………… person to believe that all men are equal irrespective of their caste, race and religion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "emotional",
                "liberal",
                "religious",
                "intolerant"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him only a week …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "past",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why are you angry",
                "why am I angry",
                "why I was angry",
                "why was I angry"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Despite receiving several warnings, he …………………….. to office on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "comes never",
                "never comes",
                "never come"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He told his wife that ……………………… Germany.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he will like to visit",
                "he is liking to visit",
                "he was liking to visit",
                "he would like to visit"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich and the influential can …………………… .. even with murder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get away",
                "get out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}